Guide to the Milton Conover Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1917-1935; Series I; 3.5; (9 boxes)
  Additional correspondence can be found in SERIES II, TOPICAL FILES, as originally maintained by Conover.
  - General
    - 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Aa - Am (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Abrahamson, Alfred, 1932-1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American Moral Forces, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - American Political Science Review, 1925-1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - American Yearbook, 1925-1933; undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - An - Az (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Anderson, William, 1927-1928; 1933 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Angell, James Rowland, 1926-1933 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Ashton, Dean H., 1926; 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Asserson, Grace P.
      General
      See: box 2, folder 31
    - Ba - Bi (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Baker, Helen Lockwood, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bates, Frank G., 1927 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Beach, Lois, 1927; 1932 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Beard, Charles A., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Bj - Bz (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Boots, Randolph S., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Brewer, William A., Jr., 1926-1927; 1932 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Burger, Sallie, 1930-1932 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Butts, A. B., 1926-1933; undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Ca - Cl (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Carter, Kerah, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Chapin, Minnie P., 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Clarke, Charles E., 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Cm - Cz (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Comer, J. P., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Commonwealth College, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Commonwealth Conferences, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Connecticut League of Women Voters, 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Connecticut Temperance and Anti-Saloon League, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Conover, Elbert, 1926-1933; undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Conover, Elisha, 1927-1937 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Conover, Samuel and Atlantic (Attie), 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Consumers League of Connecticut, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Corradini, Robert
      See: box 2, folder 50
    - Crispin, Lawrence L., 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - D - E (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Das, Jaradnath, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Davis, Jerome, 1926-1933 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Day, Clive and family, 1932; undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Dickinson, John, 1927-1930; 1934 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Dickinson College, 1926-1933; undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Dodds, Harold W., 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - F (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Fairchild, Fred R., 1928-1934 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Farnam, Henry W., 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Fisher, Irving, 1927; 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Flint, K.R.B., 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Foundation for Narcotics Research and Information, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Fuller, Clare, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Furniss, Edgar S., 1926-1934 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - G (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - General Welfare Tax League, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Graves, W. Brooke, 1926-1929; 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Gregory, Casper R., 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Griffenhagen and Associates, Ltd., 1926 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Ha - Hi (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Haig, Yemon
      See: box 1, folder 5
    - Hanway, Hannah Jane, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1925-1934; undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Hartzell, Carl, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Harvard University, 1925-1935 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Hazard, Henry B., 1926-1929; 1932 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Hj - Hz (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - I - J - K (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Institute for Government Research, 1923-1930; 1935 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Institute of Public Administration
      See: box 2, folder 59
    - Intercollegiate Prohibition Association, 1929-1935 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - International Committee of Historical Sciences, 1929-1935 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - International Institute, Y.W.C.A., 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - International Order of Good Templars, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      See also: box 1, folder 4
    - International Reform Federation, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Johns Hopkins Press, 1925-1935 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Johnson, F. I. (Mrs.), 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Kalijarvi, Thorsten, 1927; 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Kidd, Elizabeth and Joseph, 1927-1931 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - L (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Laguio, Perfecto, 1926; undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Lapp, John A., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Levitt, Albert, 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Library of Congress, Joint Committee on Materials for Research, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Lincoln, Allen B., 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Lord Baltimore Press, 1925-1930 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Louks, Merrill S., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Lovett, Sidney, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Lyon, Leverett, 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Ma - Maz (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - McBain, Howard Lee, 1927-1933 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - McClintock, Miller, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - McClure, O. J., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Me - Mz (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Mendell, Clarence W., 1926-1929; 1933-1934; undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Merriam (G. and C.) Company, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 94)
      See also: box 11, folder 267
    - Montpelier Seminary, 1926-1927; 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - N (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - National League of Women Voters, 1928-1929; 1934 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - National Municipal League, 1927-1930; 1934 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - National Rehabilitation Association
      See: box 3, folder 80
    - National Republic, 1926-1930 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - National Temperance Bureau, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Nations, Gilbert O., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - New Haven Committee for the Survey of Unemployment, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - New Haven Council of Churches, 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - New Haven Council of Religious Education, 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Norwich University
      See: box 2, folder 49
    - O (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Ogg, Frederic A.
      See: box 1, folder 6
    - Order of the Sons of Temperance, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Oxford University, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - P - Q (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Pape, William J., 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Parker, Fletcher D., 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Pi Gamma Mu, 1928-1929; 1932 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Porter, John L., 1926-1931 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Porter, Livingston, 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Powell, F. W., 1926-1929; n. d. (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Prettyman, E.C.
      See: box 2, folder 32
    - Proportional Representation League, 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - R (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Republican National Committee, 1928; 1932 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Robinson, George C., 1927-1929 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Rustan, M. B., 1926-1928 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Sa - Sm (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Scammell, J. M., 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Schmitt, Annaemae, 1925-1927; undated (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Short, Lloyd M., 1926-1929; 1934 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Smith, Darrell K., 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Sn - Sz (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1928;.1933 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Spykman, Nicholas K., 1926; 1934 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Stone, Nathan B., 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Student Christian Movement of Great Britain and Ireland, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Swedesboro (New Jersey) National Bank, 1926-1928 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Swenson, Rhinehart J., 1925-1932; 1935 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Szold, Robert, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - T (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Taylor, William Lonsdale, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Thomas, Adelaide, 1928; undated (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Travaline, Francis M., Jr., 1926; 1930; 1932 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - U-V (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - University Travel Association, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Van Netter, [underline], 1925-1932 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Veatch, Prudence, 1932-1933 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Wa - Wh (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Waterbury Republican
      See: box 4, folder 110
    - Weber, Gustavus A., 1926-1929; 1932 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Wi - Wz (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Williamson, Robert D., 1926-1929; 1933 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - x - z (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Yale Daily News, 1927; 1935 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Yale Law Journal, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Yale University, 1925-1935 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Young, James, 1926-1929; 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Zook, George F., 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Commonwealth Party
    - A (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - American Christian Alliance, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Anderson, William H.
      See: box 6, folder 153
    - Anti-Saloon League of America, 1932-1935 (Box 6, Folder 154)
      See also: box 1, folder 1
      See also: Dunford, Edward B.
      See also: box 8, folder 223
    - B (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Barnhart, Arthur, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Barton, Arthur J., 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Bierly, H. J., 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Blake, Edward E., 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 159-160)
    - C (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - Callahan, Patrick H., 1928-1934 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - "Callahan Correspondence", [ca.1930s] (Box 6, Folder 163-167)
    - Castor, Henry, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - Cavanaugh, W. W. F., 1934, undated (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - Church, Ralph E., 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - Colvin, D. Leigh, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Cooperative Commonwealth Federation, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Coulter, F. E., 1933, undated (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Davenport, Eugene, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - Davis, Murl S., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - Day, Grafton E., 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Dewey, John, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - Dinwiddie, Edwin C., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - Doak, Frances Renfrew, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - Downie, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - Drinkard, C. A., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - E-G (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - Franning, John, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - Geary, Riley W., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - Gehres, A. Walter, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - General
      - Congressional candidates, 1932, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 187)
      - Questionnaire
        - Anti-Saloon League of America, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 188)
        - General-negative, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 189)
        - General-positive, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - Griffin, A. D., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 191)
    - H-J (Box 7, Folder 192)
    - Hall, M. F., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 193)
    - Hammond, John
      See: box 8, folder 206
    - Harris, E. S., 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - Harvey, Clifford
    - Hendrickson, C. Findley, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - Holmes, Howard L., 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 196)
    - Howard, Clinton N.
      See: box 8, folder 209
    - Hunt, Fay R., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - "The Index", 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - International Reform Federation, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 199)
    - Jocoy, J. A., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 200)
    - Jones, Maro Beath, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 201)
    - L-N (Box 7, Folder 202)
    - Levitt, Albert
      See: box 3, folder 81
    - Lincoln, Allen B., 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 203)
      See also: box 3, folder 83
    - McCartney, F. M., 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - Mendenhall, Raymond E., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - National Civic League, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - National Temperance Bureau
      See: box 7, folder 179
    - National Temperance and Prohibition Council, 1934-1935; undated (Box 8, Folder 207-208)
    - National United Committee for Law Enforcement, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - National Voice, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 210-211)
    - National Voter's Union
      See: box 7, folder 204
    - National Women's Christian Temperance Union, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Nations, Gilbert O., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - O (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Ohio Union
      See: box 6, folder 158
    - P - Q (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - Parker, Fletcher D., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Peabody, Lucy W. (Mrs. Henry), 1932-1934 (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Prohibition National Committee
      See: box 6, folders 159-160
    - Prohibition State Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - R (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Richardson, B. W., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - Roberts, C. J., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - Roberts, O., 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - Russell, Howard Hyde, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - S (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - Shuler, Robert P., 1932-1934 (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - Sloan, John, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - Sons of Temperance of Connecticut, 1934-1935; undated (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - T - V (Box 8, Folder 228)
    - Temperance Federation of Arizona
      See: box 7, folder 185
    - Travers, John E., 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 229)
    - U.S. Board of Trade, 1933-1934
      See: box 6, folder 169
    - Varney, William F., 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 230)
    - W (Box 8, Folder 231)
    - Women's Christian Temperance Union (W.C.T.U.)
      - Algeo, Sara M, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 232)
      - Boole, Ella A., 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 233)
      - Coleman, Nellie Scott, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 234)
      - Colvin, Marnie W. (Box 9, Folder 235)
      - Conrad, A.E., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 236)
      - Drown, Grace K., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 237)
      - Editors, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 238)
      - Estelle, Helen G. H., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 239)
      - Frantz, Nina G., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 240)
      - Harding, E., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 241)
      - Nichols, Jennie H., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 242)
      - P - R (Box 9, Folder 243)
      - Presidents, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 244)
      - S - Z (Box 9, Folder 245)
      - Smith, Ida B. Wise, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 246)
      - Welles, Mary E., 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 247)
      - Clippings, 1934; undated (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - X - Z (Box 9, Folder 249)
- Topical Files, 1898-1935; Series II; 1.5; (3 boxes)
  This series contains correspondence, clippings, printed material, and miscellanea arranged alphabetically by organization and topic. This material was originally maintained as a separate body from SERIES I.
  - American Immigrant Institute, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 250-251)
  - American Veteran's Association, 1932-1935; undated (Box 10, Folder 252)
  - Americanization Committee of New Haven
    - Correspondence, 1931-1935; undated (Box 10, Folder 253-254)
    - Monthly reports (incomplete), 1926 January-1932 January (Box 10, Folder 255)
  - City Maps (Box 10, Folder 256)
  - Civic Federation of New Haven, 1898-1934 (Box 10, Folder 257-258)
  - Commonwealth Party
    - Clippings (Box 10, Folder 259)
    - Miscellanea (Box 10, Folder 260)
    - Platforms (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - "Courier" correspondence, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Dodge lectures, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - Independent Republican Party-lists, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 264)
  - New Haven Board of Aldermen, 1932-1933 (Box 11, Folder 265)
  - Prohibition and politics-printed material (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - State constitutions, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 267)
  - Statistics-birth and death rates, [ca.1920s] (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - U.S. Senate campaign (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Clippings, 1932
    - Bridgeport Post (Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Danbury Evening Times (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Hartford Courant (Box 12, Folder 271)
    - Meriden Record (Box 12, Folder 272)
    - New Haven Evening Register (Box 12, Folder 273)
    - New Haven Journal-Courier (Box 12, Folder 274)
    - New Haven News (Box 12, Folder 275)
    - New Haven Register (Box 12, Folder 276)
    - New Haven - Yale Daily News (Box 12, Folder 277)
    - New London - The Day (Box 12, Folder 278)
    - New York Herald-Tribune (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - New York Times (Box 12, Folder 280)
    - Norwalk Hour (Box 12, Folder 281)
    - Norwich Evening Record (Box 12, Folder 282)
    - Stamford Advocate (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - Torrington Register (Box 12, Folder 284)
    - Waterbury American (Box 12, Folder 285)
    - Waterbury Democrat (Box 12, Folder 286)
    - Waterbury Republican (Box 12, Folder 287)
    - Willimantic Chronicle (Box 12, Folder 288)
    - Windham County Transcript (Box 12, Folder 289)
    - Winsted Evening Citizen (Box 12, Folder 290)
    - Winsted Herald (Box 12, Folder 291)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Correspondence
    - Crane, Jasper, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 293)
    - Lee, Alfred, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 294)
    - Newspaper subscriptions, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 295)
    - New York Sun, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 296)
  - Press releases, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Speech-Irving Fisher's speech nominating Milton Conover, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 298)
- Teaching Materials, 1922-1935; Series III; 0.5; (2 boxes)
  This series is arranged alphabetically by type of material, i.e. course outlines, gradebooks, student papers.
  - Course outlines and lecture notes, [ca 1925-1935] (Box 13, Folder 299)
  - Departmental reports and miscellanea, [ca 1925-1935] (Box 13, Folder 300)
  - Exam questions and miscellanea, [ca 1924-1935] (Box 13, Folder 301-302)
  - Gradebooks, 1922-1929 (Box 13, Folder 303)
  - Gradebooks, 1930-1935 (Box 14, Folder 304)
  - Student papers, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 305)
  - Student reports (Box 14, Folder 306)
    - Municipal government, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 307)
    - Original sources, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 308)
- Writings and Miscellanea, 1916-1935; Series IV; 1.5; (3 boxes)
  This series is arranged in two sections: Writings and Miscellanea. Each is arranged alphabetically. Unidentified material is filed at the end of each section.
  - Writings
    - Articles-printed (Box 15, Folder 309)
    - Book reviews (Box 15, Folder 310)
    - "Civil Pensions" (Box 15, Folder 311)
    - "Commonwealth notes"
      - John Eliot's "The Christian Commonwealth" (Box 15, Folder 312)
      - General (Box 15, Folder 313-315)
    - "The Development of Civil Pensions in the United States", M.A. thesis, University of Minnesota, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 316)
    - "Dry Tides" (Box 15, Folder 317)
    - "Municipal Corporations" (Box 16, Folder 318-319)
    - "New Jersey the American" (Box 16, Folder 320)
    - "Source Problems in Municipal Government" (Box 16, Folder 321)
    - Speeches, [ca 1930s] (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - "State Forestry Developments" (Box 16, Folder 323)
    - "Working Manual of Original Sources in American Government"
      - Draft (Box 16, Folder 324)
      - Printed copy (Box 16, Folder 325)
    - Unidentified writings and notes (Box 16, Folder 326-328)
  - Miscellanea
    - Appointment books (Box 17, Folder 329-331)
    - Clippings
      - City management-New Haven, 1932-1933 (Box 17, Folder 332)
      - Colleges, 1932-1934 (Box 17, Folder 333)
      - Conover, Samuel S., [ca 1917] (Box 17, Folder 334)
      - Military service, [ca 1917-1920] (Box 17, Folder 335)
      - National economy, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 336)
      - Yale and miscellaneous, 1924-1935; undated (Box 17, Folder 337)
    - Genealogical data, 1924-1929; undated (Box 17, Folder 338)
    - Marshall, Helen Edith - "The Social Philosophy of William Jennings Bryan", 1926 (Box 17, Folder 339)
    - Notebooks, 1936; undated (Box 17, Folder 340)
    - Passports, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 341)
    - Photographs, [ca 1932] (Box 17, Folder 342)
    - Printed material - Yale and miscellanea, undated (Box 17, Folder 343)